You don't hit a deposit, you enter
deposit. Yeah. Now you just hit AFS to
add filter size.
>> If you do if if you do FS, it will just
do like um filter size, but because
>> and then enter to resume.
>> Yeah, it just resumes it.
[clears throat]
>> How did I not know about this?
>> Well, so this is why we're doing this
episode, right? [music]
>> Best part of Viking when you can just,
you know, critical think, right?
Yeah, dude.
>> All right, hackers. The ad read is going
to get a little technical today, so
buckle up for this, okay? I'm going to
tell you exactly how Threat Locker is
screwing hackers at every step along the
way with dynamic access controls,
preventing even port scans from
happening on threat locker networks. So,
uh, let's let's dive into it. There's
three primary ways that Threat Locker
implements this. I'm going to give you
guys two for this for this quick read.
Um, and hopefully you'll be able to
understand how exactly they're
preventing hackers from doing port
scans. Um, so first one is called local
challenge. This is on the common
scenario where a computer wants to
connect to a network resource and
they're on the same network. So, what's
going to happen is over you know this
this threat locker handshake uh the
computer is going to send a request to
the server. the server is going to
respond with a challenge and then uh the
computer has to you know complete that
challenge and provide a response back to
the server before the SMB port is even
opened up to that specific computer
right so you can't do any port scanning
or anything like that because you're not
going through this handshake with the
computer um so that's that's one way the
next way is in like remote work
scenarios where your laptop is like you
know out on some Wi-Fi or whatever and
you still need to access network
resources um in this scenario the
computer is going to shoot an I, you
know, authenticated IP change up to the
threat locker cloud. Then when it
requests access to a specific server,
maybe it's trying to get in by like RDS
or whatever if it's if it's uh in a
remote work scenario, the RDS server,
you know, before it opens up that port
is going to query the allow list in the
threat locker cloud and say, "Hey, uh,
this IP is trying to connect. What
should I do with him?" Um, and then
threat Locker Cloud will give them a yes
or no on that and they'll open or close
the port based on that response. Okay.
So, with Threat Locker in place, really,
you can't even do port scans, guys. So,
tell you what, let's go back to the show
and hack something easier. And we'll let
Threat Locker do their thing. All right.
All right. Let's go.
All right. Subhackers. Before we jump
into the episode, we got the this
weekend bug bounty segment. We've got
actually quite a few items this week.
The first of which is an exciting one.
Hacker One has launched the netscaler
program which is a really cool
opportunity for those of you guys that
like to go after the you know asset
notesque um attacking enterprise
applications or appliances or whatever.
Um in scope is the netcaler gateway the
netcaler ADC netcaler AAA um and they
have treasure maps and credentials for
each of these. Um, it's a public
program. Lows are 300, medium 600, high
iss 4,000, crits 10,000. Not bad. Um,
definitely something that you guys
should look at if you're interested in
those sort of enterprise applications.
Um, going after this. Um, next up is
from Yes, We Hack. We have the ultimate
guide to bug bounty HTTP request
smuggling vulnerabilities.
Um, like I've said in the past, guys,
everybody has been sleeping on Yes, we
hack educational content. It is super
freaking good. Um, so if you're looking
to sort of uh clean up your knowledge on
HTB request mugings, something that
intimidates a lot of hackers from what
I've heard, um, this would be a great
place to do it. It's very thorough, very
long, very detailed. Um, really good
place to, uh, clean up your knowledge on
HP request mumbling. So, we'll link that
down in the description. Um also uh this
is coming from bug crowd. Uh there have
been some changes to the request a
response feature in bug crowd. Um and
this is when you know you need you need
some feedback from the program. Um and
previously this was uh this feature was
limited to one request open at a time.
That has been bumped to two and you can
request a response on submissions in
theformational state. So they're
expanding that a little bit which I
think is cool. Right? they are creating
more overhead for themselves to give you
a voice, right? I just wanted to
highlight that for you guys because I
just think that's that's good guy Bug
Crowd um really caring about the hacker
there. In addition to that, Bug Crowd
also re released a hacker spotlight
recently for Evan Connelly uh who is one
of my favorite hackers out there. Um,
and this is a great read as well if
you're interested in getting to know uh
the pastor and hacker uh which I think
is a really cool um personality that
Evan's got there. Um, so it's a good
read. I recommend it. Last but not
least, um, I wanted to point out a
couple positions that are actually open
in Epic Games. Now I collaborated
closely um you know worked with the Epic
game teams uh really closely in the past
live hacking event and um I got to know
a little bit of the team and they are
recruiting for some really cool roles.
One is senior manager threat
intelligence and offensive security um
and the other one is EOSc programmer
intern. Okay. Um both of these are
really good opportunities. They're um
located in Kerry uh North Carolina. Um,
and so if you're interested, if you're
in that area or you're interested about
um, hopping into these, uh, we're going
to link these at the website um,
jobs.ctb.show.
Okay, jobs.ctb.show.
There we are. Right there. So, we've got
those on there. I would definitely
recommend working with the team. They're
amazing. Um, if either of those titles
sound good to you. All right, let's go.
Let's hop to the show.
>> There was kind of two things. One was I
just think this is a really funny story
for my daughter. the uh I I thought of
it when I saw myself wearing a black
shirt today. I was like, "Oh, I don't
think I'd ever told Justin that story."
But uh we were at her cross country meet
and I she was walking behind me talking
with a friend and I heard her say her
friend asked like, "Oh, who's your dad
or which one's your dad?" And uh my
daughter Sailor pointed and said, "Uh,
oh, he's the one in the black shirt. He
almost always wears black. He's a
hacker."
>> I was like, [laughter] "Yes,
>> yes, that's me."
>> Yeah. I thought that was funny. Kids,
kids are hilarious, man. I uh Yeah. Uh
one of my kids was writing a little, you
know, essay for school and she was
talking about my job and I was like,
"You got to put ethical in front of
hacker, [laughter] you know, cuz they're
like, uh, yeah, my dad's a hacker. He
works really hard at it. He loves it."
You know, that sort of thing. And I was
like, their image is like me over here
like scamming people and like working
really hard as a hacker, stealing money
and [laughter] stuff.
>> That's so funny. And honestly, like with
the some of the bugs you found around
CSS injection for like credit card
leaks, it's like you could be
>> legit at that. But
>> no, yeah, I wanted to before we hop into
the episode talk about the live hacking
event for just a second.
>> Yeah.
>> Um
>> I don't know. We don't we since we're
live, we don't have to necessarily talk
too much about it if you don't want to
share. But I feel like I had a
self-realization. I just struggled with
do I go solo or do I be on a team for
the last like three or four events
>> and I have kind of just I don't know had
mixed results or mixed success and then
this time I was like I want to hack with
literally everyone like Justin's in this
event Ronnie's in this event. Kieran and
BuzzFactor are in this event. A bunch of
people from like Plyes B team six are in
this event. I want to hack with all of
them.
>> I didn't know that.
>> Yeah, there's like there's like five or
six of them and half of them have never
been to a hacking event before and so
it's really cool. But anyways, so I
basically just like didn't commit. And
then within one day of being into the
event, I was like, I should have just
committed. This is like such a struggle
and it's so annoying. And I think it's
just my personality type. I know you are
a big fan of like at least until Duke
window ends solo hacking, but I think
it's just 100% personality related
because what I did was I buddied up with
like one of the more talented B team 6
guys who's never been to live hacking
event before. And it wasn't like he fed
me the bug. In fact, he had nothing to
do with one of the bugs that I found,
but we immediately found two bugs. one I
found basically solo but just like
because I was like communicating with
him and because I was much more
energized and excited about the event
having like someone I'm hacking with I
immediately found a bug and then we
found one together that was like like
pretty incredible too and so anyways I
think I'm just going to like stop trying
to be solo unless for some reason I
don't know I have to but I think that
for me it's just like
>> I feel so much more motivated,
energized, excited and work harder when
I'm with other people. So
>> yeah, man. I think I think it depends on
your personality type. And I also think
this event is kind of like very well
aligned to your
>> skill set and your your hype, you know.
Um, so I think this could definitely be
a fun one for you to to play with, you
know, and and at the end of the day,
man, you know, when we've reached the
point that we're at, it's kind of like,
well, I might as well do it for fun, you
know? It's like it's like we don't we
don't have to you know like I think
there's a lot to being content and you
know a lot of value to being content and
then you know making decisions that are
not necessarily the most optimized for
winning the live hacking event or cash
return you know but I had a lot of fun
with my friends and I found bugs that
I'm proud of you know that sort of
thing.
>> Yep. Sweet dude.
>> Yep. All right. So, that being said, we
are in the middle of a live hacking
event and uh and so we have some hacking
to do today and I'm realizing actually I
am
>> wearing the wrong glasses. I don't know
if you guys know this, I actually have
special glasses for my CTV episode that
don't reflect.
>> Oh, that's cool.
>> Yeah. So, I'm going to switch into
those. But um yeah, so let's let's get
into the uh let's get into the meat of
the content today so we can get back
because I was just telling you right
before I got on this call, I was like,
man, I want to hack so much right now. I
have a a PC exploit like primed and I
haven't like and it's ready to press,
you know, test on it and I I'm waiting
till I get done with this uh to test it.
So um it's going [clears throat] to be a
pooa. Uh all right. You want to you want
to start out with um with some of the
stuff you got or do you want me to start
with one?
>> Sure. Yeah. So, I mean, let's just set
the stage real quick. Basically, this
episode is going to be I thought this
was a good idea. I suggested it to
Justin. I again, maybe it's a
personality thing, but I'm just obsessed
with like uh ways to make myself more
efficient. Like, I've just kind of
always been obsessed with efficiency.
And uh one of the best things I've
noticed that I take away from other
hackers is basically watching them work.
anytime I'm screen sharing or
collaborating with other hackers,
they're doing things that are like, "Oh,
wow. If I had known that, I could have
saved so much more time. I would have
like found more bugs or been more
efficient or whatever."
>> And I was like, "This would make a great
uh episode." And I think you and Justin
or you and Joel actually almost like a
year ago or a year and a half ago did an
episode where you kind of talked about
something light. It was more like kind
of like scripts or like you know the
best tool for certain jobs or something.
And so this will probably feel similar
to listeners to that episode. But I
think that uh cumulatively all of these
like little like efficiency hacks are
going to make you a much better, faster,
more efficient hacker because honestly
some of that boredom and some of that
downtime can not only make you like like
make you slower, but it also can make
you lose motivation.
>> I don't know like if you've noticed
that, but sometimes it's like if there's
a barrier to entry to like doing the
next thing. Oh yeah. You always say
reduce the friction or remove the
friction. When there's that friction
there, you basically just don't test for
things you should be testing for.
>> 100%. Yeah. you you've got to figure out
a way to optimize these things. And I
was actually working with Matias the
other day on a bug, Matias Carlson, and
you know, like before I even really knew
that there like I was very confident
there was a bug there. He was like,
"Hey, dude, we've got to automate this
whole test process like
>> you know, like and I was like, well, I
think maybe we should validate it
first." you know, validate this one
pivotal piece first and then and then,
you know, we'll go back and build the
the like, you know, um harness or
whatever and like, you know, get this
exploit testing um accelerated. And he's
like, "Nah, dude. I'm like really
confident. We got to do it right now."
And I was like, "All right, like I'll
I'll I'll do it." And lo and behold, you
know, like it would have taken me
probably hours of, "Oh, I'm so close to
just validating. Oh, I'm so close to
validating it. I'm so close to
validating it." you know, uh, and I was
so glad that I had it automated that
whole time, you know. So, I definitely
think, uh, investing in that automation
pays dividends.
>> Yeah, because your initial attempt that
you thought was going to work once shot,
it had a little error and then you fix a
little error and then you fix a little
error and it just keeps going, right?
And and each attempt takes so long that
and I find that to be the case in this
live event that we're in right now
because the setup is so honorous for
some of these things to test. you do
have to set up like a big long thing or
you know and with a lot of um just AI
related bugs. I know oftentimes you're
having to like clear the chat or delete
all your messages in the queue, you
know, like a lot of these the things are
really difficult to do. So
>> yeah. All right. Well, let's let's jump
into it. Um okay, dude. I I'm just gonna
pick on you right off the bat. So your
first one is even better auto decoding,
right?
>> Yes.
>> Okay, dude. So, but you know, right by
the time this episode airs, I think
Kaida will have released the new convert
feature. Have you seen that?
>> I have seen you all talking about it. I
haven't used it yet.
>> Okay. Yeah. So, it's like a little
drawer at the bottom of Kaido that does
like kind of what inspector does in
Burp, right? Yes.
>> Um, but it's got some additional uh nice
nice features in there. So, um but yeah,
I totally agree. some sort of like auto
decoding or something that allows you to
see easier what you're working on in an
encoded environment is like super
essential.
>> Well, so the reason why this came up, I
was actually on a sales call with like
with Kaido and we were like showing it
to somebody and you know they were like
you they they asked if there was a
plugin the equivalent to um
>> oh man what's the one where you can use
like custom tags in your actual request
>> hackverter because obviously that's a
really good thing and it's like what no
we don't have a hacker equivalent yet.
I'm sure we will pretty soon, but why
have I not needed that? And it was like
really frustrating to me why I've not
needed hackverter. And I like thought
about it. I thought about it and I even
opened up Burp and started using it. I
was like, I know sometimes I have to
edit inside of like URL encoding and
it's like, oh, even better just has the
thing here. I just edit it over there.
It auto updates and then I resend the
request. And so any anytime I need to do
like quick edits that's way edits that
way. That's how I always do it. And so
anyways, I just wanted to mention that
because I'm sure there are some people
out there who are painstakingly copying
and pasting out of replay.
>> Yeah. Yeah. And I think for right now
that is a good solution. Um probably by
the time this episode airs the new
convert uh uh drawer will be available
in Kaido which is going to have some
really awesome features. So I think
that'll be one of the things that are is
near the top of my list. But actually
I've got a different solution that I use
for that. So, this is actually what I
was hoping we would do in this
discussion was I was hoping you would
point out things that I could do even
more efficiently.
>> Oh, okay. So, this is just a reszo like
Reszo's like, "Hey, Justin, I've got an
idea. [laughter]
What if we go on the pod and talk about
>> You give me all your secrets." Yeah,
exactly. Just teasing out your secrets
here. Well, dude, I think it's also
really awesome that I don't know, you
know, how much the community knows the
history of of your interactions with the
pod, but like, you know, Reza was like
every episode as soon as it come out, he
would listen to it, give us feedback,
you know, send messages, like retweet,
and uh right actually on on the like
deck that we have when we talk to
sponsors, like on the first page is like
a glowing review from Reszo. Uh,
>> like if you're not listening to the pod,
you're doing it wrong or something.
>> Exactly. Yeah. Yeah. And I'm like, and
we were working on updating the slides
the other day and we're like, "Oh, well,
I guess we got to take this out because
it just looks like our own co-host,
>> right?" Yeah, exactly. It just looks
like you. Yeah,
>> but it's great. Anyway, what I was going
to say was um that actually what I've
started doing is using the Kaido command
pallet to do these encodings um which
has been pretty solid. So, uh I I did a
PR to um Even Better uh when was this?
Like, uh back towards Defcon, I think.
And uh for those of you that don't know,
even better is like just like couple UI
customizations, that sort of thing to
Kaido. Um and what the PR does is it
adds all of the convert workflows to the
command pallet and allows you to use
them inside of your um repeater uh you
know equivalent, right? For those of you
using Burp, um the the replay uh window.
So you can just highlight some stuff and
then you just press control K B 64 and
then you press enter and it you know B
64s encodes whatever you've you've got.
>> Um and so that's been really solid for
me like I just it's something that feels
really right to use you know and like I
don't really have to think about it. I
just say okay control K basics for
control K you're all you know and it
just does it you know. Yeah.
>> Um,
>> so that's been that's been pretty solid
for me. But I I think that's I'm also
going to add in there, one of the things
that I hope to make a PR for soon is um
also adding all of the named replay tabs
in there.
>> So you can just do commit, you know,
control K or command K and then just say
like that one request and it and press
enter and then it jumps to that replay
tab,
>> you know. So yeah,
>> I feel like it could get busy and big
repo like, you know, it might get noisy,
but that's still a good idea.
>> Oh, for sure. especially with the auto
rename feature from shift, right? Like
that's that is uh you know all of them
are renamed to something a little bit
more reasonable now,
>> right?
>> Um but I think I think that has
increased the efficiency of my workflow
a good bit.
>> Yeah, that's awesome.
>> Um so yeah, you mentioned command pallet
from Kaido. Um one thing I wanted to
mention, this is like kind of uh almost
silly, but I think that it is going to
probably help a lot of people who have
like never had a way to do this in the
past. In Chrome DevTools, you can right
click on a node in the DOM and do edit
as HTML. I'm sure a lot of people
already know that, but it has been
really helping me in two ways. One way
is um there are often times that you're
setting up a project or a landing page
or hacking together like some sort of
like bug bounty tool and the like your
um AI assistant like whether it's Cloud
Code or Codeex just can't like it
doesn't know what's wrong or it's trying
to fix some UI or CSS thing. And I've
just realized that what I'll often do is
go in there and just like select like
the the parent element like a couple
parent elements up that as HTML, copy
and paste in there, complain about it,
and it increases the odds of a fix like
very significantly.
>> Oh, totally.
>> Because it has like it has all the HTML.
And [snorts] then u and it's able to
kind of correlate that with whatever
code is generating the HTML at the time.
Um, and then the other thing I've used
it for is actually in this live hacking
event, there are a lot of um, scoping
and policy documents and setup
documents. I'll say it nicely. And um,
some of them are in an app where you
actually can't download. You know how
sometimes with Google Drive, for
example, you can set something where
it's like not downloadable or copy and
pasteable. And that was like pretty
annoying to me because I wanted to give
all that context to AI to like start
asking things about the scope or
whatever. just like help with like
justifying um certain bugs and stuff
like that. I knew I would need it
throughout this event. And so I just
rightclicked edit HTML, copy and paste
that into an HTML converter online. Like
there's plenty of HTML to markdown
converters. And then I saved that off
into a markdown note so that a I could
reference it very easily. And you know
that whole process took like 3 seconds
whereas I can see some people struggling
or not even being able to figure out how
to do it without like doing a screenshot
or printing the page. And then
>> yeah.
>> Yeah,
>> it gets complicated for sure. I think uh
I think I definitely do that exact same
thing and I and two two things that I
wanted to say on that that I've been
thinking oh I should improve this in my
own hacking workflow
>> is apparently now cursor you can hook
your browser into cursor
>> and it like has access to the page that
you're on and can look at the DOM
>> I think it has its own browser as of
like yesterday.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, it has its own
browser, too. And um and I that's just
such a game changer for Kaido dev
>> cuz like now literally you can just be
like, "Okay, it's not centered. Fix it."
And it and it like
>> I never thought about loading Kaido in
there because since Kaido's browser
based. Yeah.
>> Yeah. It can just look directly at
Kaido. Um which is awesome. Uh so I'm
definitely going to have a lot of fun
with that. But the other one, dude,
while I was investigating what you were
saying just a second ago, I noticed
this. So, um, open up DevTools and
select like a, you know, a field or
whatever. Right click on it and there's
this like thing that is debug with AI
that has a little new thing next to it
and you hit start chat and it just jump
dumps it into Gemini in the dev tool.
>> Nice. That's cool. Yeah, I knew there
was AI in dev tools, but you would have
to like ask it about the element. It
would have to like go find it. That's
cool that you can just right click on
one.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I think that could be really
solid for like understanding, you know,
why something is operating the way that
it is or um stuff like that. I always
also use edit as HTML to check I don't
know why I always do it but I always
check whether like the less than sign is
uh is actually URL encoded or not or or
um HTML encoded or not
>> because I'll see it in there and I'm
like well you know less than space is
not a valid tag name so maybe it's not
encoded you know but it's definitely
encoded always so yeah
>> that's actually interesting you brought
that up because I was always curious
what how people did that who were like
front end people since it shows up as a
normal
um angle bracket there.
>> Yeah. Actually, as we're talking about
this, I'm going to go and do the thing
that I uh I
was going to talk about next, which is
uh the I actually have a set of tools
that I use for like client side stuff.
Um and I've got them on my on my web
server under like quick tools is what
I've got it called. Um, but essentially
what it does is it I have like a set of
tools that will allow me to just get XSS
on my own page, right? I've got a set of
tools that will do a window.open. I've
got one that will do a window.open in a
null, you know, null origin. I've got
something that will iframe something.
I've got something that will iframe and
then like apply some sandbox properties.
I've got like some redirect scripts. All
of that stuff is sort of bundled into a
toolkit that I call quick tricks.
>> Yeah.
>> Uh, you know, and and I think having
those there, especially like the
window.open ones where, okay, I know I
need this window reference,
>> so I'm just going to like hit it, throw
it into my window. Script. I know that
it's, you know, the variable is always
named J or whatever, so I can like send
a post message easily through through
DevTools or whatever. Um, having those
in place really minimizes the amount of
time it takes for you to test something.
Yeah. Um, and then I've also got like
this this test.html
file that's got like a nice code mirror
editor like in it and then renders
whatever I type in a you know iframe
right beneath it so that I can like very
dynamically test how certain things are
rendered or how JavaScript is affecting
the DOM inside of that little you know
debug environment.
>> Yeah, dude. That's sick. Yeah, I'm sure
the community is going to beg you to
release it now, but [laughter]
>> Well, and and it I I I think I've
released it to the critical thinkers. If
not, I will. Um, but uh it also takes it
automatically. This is then other cool
piece is it takes the script
>> and it puts it automatically in the hash
>> encoded. So I was like if once I find
the thing that I want I can just copy it
and be like
>> Joseph check this out and then it loads
everything up for you and you can see
exactly what I saw.
>> Yeah. Honestly, there are probably other
places where that um what's that called?
where that like flow could be pretty
helpful, you know, like places where
like kind of like cyershe or whatever,
like anything that puts the content of
the thing in the in the URL bar or or in
the hash.
>> Um, so that you could automatically
>> shareability really easily if it's not
like a massive mega script, you know.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. In fact, I was going to mention
that, so I'll go ahead and mention it
now. But I still use Cyberchef
sometimes, like pretty frequently. Um,
recently I've been using it for like
some AI hacking. um not for this event,
but just in general, there are um often
what are called, you know, Q params. I
think I mentioned this last week on the
pod, but
>> yeah, and oftentimes if you have a query
that's being passed in as a get
parameter and you're wanting to like
iterate on it a bunch or like load it as
like a CSRF or like or like basically
test as like a one-click um as like a
oneclick vulnerability, you're like very
frequently having to do, you know, URL
encoding on your prompt. And so I'll
just have like a Cyberchef, you know,
tab up and I'll just like edit my prompt
and then I'll have it automatically URL
encode and and appended to the to the
URL. And so then I can just copy and
paste the thing at the bottom and it
just allows me to work like really
quickly. Um, so anyways, if people
haven't heard of Cyber Chef, it's
definitely worth like playing with and
using. Um, it's almost always for me
just like find or replace. I often will
also use it. I don't know if you have
like a It's a good question for you,
Justin. If you're if you have like an
HTTP response that is like JSON um
escaped
>> um where all of like you know your
quotes are are all like protected and
maybe it's all like on one line with
like slash ends like um or back slashn
for new line characters. How do you then
like get it in like a human readable uh
view before you like are able to test it
or hack with it?
>> Dude, this is a this is a you know
somebody hacks when they ask this
question, right? Like this is the real
[__] question that like [laughter]
that like only the guy that's like damn
this stupid like JSON code.
>> Yes, exactly. It's so annoying to parse
visually. I got to go like put in
Cybersh. And that's what I do. But I'm
curious what other people do.
>> Yeah. Um so I've got a couple solutions
for this. Sometimes I'll just like paste
it into DevTools and have it render the
object
>> and then like you know or or do like a
JSON uh you know parse on it.
>> Oh, interesting.
>> Or JSON load from from the um the dev
tools. Mhm.
>> Uh but actually I've also got another
toolkit that I that actually integrates
nicely into my next thing that I was
going to talk about in Raycast. Okay. So
Raycast is like the um I think I've I've
ranted about it on the pod before, but
it's like a really awesome um command
pallet tool for your OS, right? So you
you pop it in there. Um I've got a
custom I've got a custom script for it
that I have bound to Gez, I don't even
know what I have what do I have it bound
to? I've got it to Windows key space.
Um, and then that drops me right into my
like uh my tool. And let me just read
you some of these tools that I've got.
So, um, in here I've got the following
commands. I've got CVSS, which opens up
CVS advisor for me to calculate that.
I've got pydrops into a Python console.
I've got uh checks, which opens up uh
the the clipboard content in a hex
editor. I've got ced edit, which opens
it in a text editor. I've got C command
which pipes the current clipboard
content into a command and then copies
it back out. I've got cookie which takes
the current HTTP request that I've got
and redacts the cookies in the header.
>> Oh, that's sick.
>> Right. Which is helpful for pasting
stuff into the like a report
>> or into AI or whatever.
>> Yeah. I've got JWT and then I paste in
the token and it puts it in JWT.io. I've
got um URL encode all, which is
different than uh URL encode because
>> I often want that.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And it's very hard to
find stuff that will actually do it.
It's weird.
>> It does.
>> Um I've got an OCR one. And then these
are the ones, dude. These are the ones
that are hype. Okay, listen to this. So,
I've got one called Mr, which is just
match and replace in the clipboard. So,
I open up the command palette. I type MR
space whatever I want to find. Space
whatever I want to replace.
>> Right. So it's kind of like said
>> Yeah, exactly. And and but it just does
it really
>> but it happens on the clipboard and it
puts it back on the clipboard. Yeah, you
told me this before. Yes.
>> It's crazy.
>> I I do this I do that exact thing with
one of the tools I was going to mention.
If you have more you can mention it but
yeah I I wanted to mention to the
audience if they didn't know at least on
Mac OS there is a command called PB
paste and PB copy. And so I use that all
the time if I have something on the
clipboard and I want to do a match
replace. I just like we'll have the I'll
open the terminal do PB uh paste pipe
then like my said command
>> and then pipe and then PB copy and so it
just paste it in you know it pipes it to
the replacement and then it pipes it
about to the copy. That's interesting
you have the same thing in Raycast.
>> Yeah, I've just got it built right into
Raycast there. So I can just do Mr. Boom
boom and and you're good. Right. So I'll
often use this for like getting rid of
new line characters or something like
that in like a like a GraphQL query or
something like that. Right? Like for
example, if you grab a GraphQL query and
it's got all the, you know, back slash
ends or whatever. Yes. And you want to
actually like see it.
>> Yep.
>> Um you can use the Kaido plugin for that
now. But uh if you want to actually, you
know, just have it in a text file or
whatever and see it how it is,
>> um then you can just use, you know, MR
to to replace the backslash with an
actual back slashn. Uh and that will do
it. So
>> you can tell it's a GraphQL query by the
way it is.
>> Exactly. Yeah. [laughter] You can tell
it's an Aspen by the way that it is. Uh,
I love that. Um, but one more thing on
this raycast thing that I had was I've
actually also got um I've also got a
subcomand called text transforms. And
what it does is it looks directly at the
string that I've entered into my like
custom command pallet. And if it's a q,
w zx, er, c or v, [laughter]
uh, it will apply that transformation to
it. So for example, if I if I hit QQ,
that's gonna double URL encode. You
know, Q is URL encode, Q is URL encode,
right? So it's going to double URL
encode it, right? And then if I type QW,
>> then that's going to URL encode, URL
encode, URL decode.
>> Right? And then if I add QWA, URL
encode, URL encode, URL decode, B64
encode.
>> Nice. Yeah.
>> Right. So you can create these like sort
of muscle memored um you know uh just
strings that represent patterns of
encoding.
>> Uh and then the system will just do it
and then pop it right back into your
clipboard.
>> That's really cool. Yeah. I like the way
that you basically view your clipboard
as like an object that can be uh
modified.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I think that's essential for
for you know being able to automate
these things quickly. I
>> I think most people don't though. I
would say most people paste it
somewhere, transform it, and then put it
back. But you're like just transforming
it in place, which is really cool.
>> Yeah. [snorts]
Yeah, that is I think that is a unique a
unique factor there. I also use ray
raycast like native features like uh
like quick links and stuff like that for
like a lot of the CTVB stuff that I go
to pretty often. And I'm really bummed
that Gemini does not have have a Q
parameter because uh like I would love
to set up like a custom Gemini
uh command in Raycast where I could just
you know open Raycast query Gemini and
then have it open up in a new tab but it
doesn't
>> I've got something for you.
>> Do you
Okay. What? What? Do you have a cube
parameter for Gemini?
>> Maybe.
>> What are [snorts] you DMing me? No,
that's somebody else. Okay. I was like,
"What the heck?"
>> I'll message Jeff for the pod.
>> Okay. Yeah, that sounds good. Raycast
does have AI built into it, though,
which I do use sometimes. Uh, but I just
prefer Pure Gemini.
>> I'm going to rant for 30 seconds on this
thing. There are so many um command
pallets right now on my computer. I have
like there's like an auto pop-up one for
claude and an auto auto pop pop pop-up
one for chat GPT atlas and I have one
for raycast and then like when I'm in
shift it also has you know there's like
or sorry when I'm in Kaido there's like
one for shift and there's a regular
command pallet and um anyways my brain
is a little bit um overstimulated with
that um kind of sort of on that topic uh
actually it doesn't matter I was going
to mention that I installed omari on an
old Linux thing and I was trying to
anyways doesn't matter I'm just going to
stay on Mac so
>> yeah what did okay no Now you got it.
You baited me. Tell me about Omari
because I've seen it around.
>> It's just like Arc. It's like Do you say
Arch or Arc? I don't know.
>> Okay. It's it's it's Arc Linux but in
easy mode. You don't have to actually
configure all the things. It puts you in
like a default install that's like
already kind of sort of pretty
>> and DHH in kind of invented Omari. It's
really cool.
>> Um [snorts]
actually I will spend another 30 seconds
on this kind of um cool story because I
felt proud of myself. But basically, I
have a my old Lenovo laptop is dual
boot. Um, and the Linux side is disc
encrypted and I had Ubuntu on there and
then I had Windows uh installed on the
other partition that I used to play
Minecraft with the kids because I just,
you know, sometimes you need Windows.
>> Yeah.
>> And um so when I wanted to install
Omari, I was like, "Oh, I'm sure I can
just pick the, you know, the Ubuntu
partition. It'll just install." Great.
It did not.
>> [snorts]
>> And so they say on their website like oh
if the uh Omari default installer like
you use like an ISO USB bootable USB.
It's like if that doesn't work then you
have to install it manually and all you
do is you install Arc Linux and then you
run this script that then like
customizes it to basically be like
Omari.
>> So then I I tried to use the Arc Linux
ISO in bootable installer. It also
doesn't work if you have partitions like
that. So anyways I ended up like
manually running commands to like um
install it without the installer. I
basically installed Arc Linux from
scratch without an installer like
without even using the Arc Linux
installer and it took like two hours.
But anyways, now I have a Marky on on my
Lenovo and I'm going to play with it
sometime,
>> dude. Yeah, you know, I I had a season
of like I'm going to customize all my
stuff and you know, like it was was
running that as well.
>> And then I was like actually I don't
want to do this, you know, like all I
want is everything to work so that I
could focus on hacking, you know, like
>> Exactly. Reduce friction to hack.
>> Yeah. Exactly. So I just install, you
know, freaking out of the box YUbuntu
and just, you know,
>> Yeah. or Debian, you know, nothing
something that no bloat and then just do
it, you know.
>> Exactly.
>> Yeah. All right. Um, let's see. Uh,
dude, this one's a good one. Why don't
you talk about that one?
>> Uh, sure. Yeah. Can you How do you
strike out in Google Docs? You have it
up there and it's so clean and I can't
even find it in my UI.
>> I got you. It's format
text.
>> Got it.
>> And then strike third.
>> Gotcha. They need to make it as a quick
button, but anyways,
>> they totally do. Yeah. Okay. Yeah, I
wanted to do it for these ones. Anyways,
okay guys. Yeah, the one thing I wanted
to mention here because I still think
there are probably not enough people
using it, although I'm sure some people
out there know about it is the FFUF-
request flag. Um FFUF is probably still
my favorite tool besides, you know, um
proxy and um I still use it all the
time. And I think that, you know,
widescale recon is a pretty busy place
right now. like it's hard to be the
first person to find a domain and then
to fuzz and all the things and not get
banned by you know nearly every company
has Cloudflare now or you know something
else ai in front of it so you're often
going to get rate limited and banned
anyways but one thing that I feel like
basically very few hackers are doing
well is doing content discovery and
fuzzing especially of like APIs post
authentication and some people are right
they'll they'll they'll use automate or
they'll use intruder but it is not um
trivial and often you'll like quickly
get rate limited or banned and when
you're hacking on your own machine on
your own public Wi-Fi I feel like most
people are just hesitant to do it
because it's like and if I get a waff
ban now it's going to affect my ability
to watch Hulu or my kids ability and so
I feel like people probably aren't doing
it as much as they could and should but
one thing that makes it really easy is
the dash request flag in uh FFUF so you
can just copy and paste an entire raw
HTTP request with your cookies or your O
token if it's an API request and
>> um Then I just like have my BPS up in a
terminal. I paste the command in. I
already have like a bash alias that uses
the dash request flag with the file name
like req.ext or req. And so then I like
I just always save the request as that
file name. And then I can just use my
bash alias to automatically use that
file in the current folder. And so now I
can just like fuzz with my personal
quickheads list at, you know, as quick
and as easily as like, oh, copy and
paste out of Kaido. Bam, run it. Copy
paste out of Kaido. And I could probably
just write a credto plugin that would
just do that. Right click FFU F this or
whatever at some point. But um it's
already so fast it's like it doesn't
save me that much time to do that.
>> Yeah, you can actually do it with a with
a workflow as well. Um you know, you
don't even have to do a plugin. You can
just do an active workflow and that do
it too. And you could launch that active
workflow from the from the command
pallet. Uh but what I was going to say
was with this new version of Kaido as
well, we they've got the save to file
>> uh uh you know built in now. So if you
hit if you right click save to file,
it'll drop it into the file and then you
can run fuff from there.
>> Um so that that's another optimization
to that. But I totally use the dash
request thing all the time as well. That
is like one of my most commonly used
>> uh forms of puff to be honest.
>> You know, one thing I want to just as
like a maybe a thing for the community
or maybe this could be built into Kaido.
Sometimes I'll want to um basically have
an hack verter for FFUF, you know, like
>> I want to like uh request with a file
like a raw HTTP file and then also have
like you know the payload that it's
inserting in for the word list be
wrapped in like a hacker tag. So anyways
be interesting.
>> Yeah. Yeah, that would be interesting. I
think I think uh yeah I'm wondering
how
>> I mean the way that Kaido auto already
automatically what's it called processes
payloads
>> is probably already the ide
>> um no I'm just talking about by default
like you know URL encoding as a
pre-processor.
>> Oh yeah yeah pre-processors. Yeah.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. You could definitely do
that. But I mean at the end of the day
it's you know I mean kind of is rushed
so you know I don't know maybe it is
faster than uh than puff but puff I
think you know has been very optimized
for speed right. Um
>> and yeah I don't know I guess it's not
within my workflow to like use automate
to fuzz for something you know like you
know do directory brute forcing. It it
is for fuzzing actually but not for
directory brute forcing. So maybe
there's some uh some integration there
that would be good like you know you set
up like your fuff harness on the server
and then like connect it back to Kaido
and and have it you know you might even
be able to do have it generate word
lists like it does where it processes
the specific injection points like with
a convert workflow or with a
pre-processor and then goes from there.
>> Yeah, it would be really neat if it came
back and like dropped it in findings too
if it like had a hit or something. It'd
be like a cool flag. It's such a process
though for me like typically with fuff
I'm I'll run it and then I'll see like
okay you know every I'm not interested
in anything that's size 92 you know so
then you do whatever FS92 you know and
and then and
>> well it's AFS right it's like hit enter
AFS because you can add file size or do
you control C it and then change it
>> oh I control C it do you
>> yeah there's a new thing where you just
hit enter
>> you just hit enter it pauses it and then
you just and it like drops you into like
a little [__] F um like input input
shell
>> and you do and you do AFS for add file
size.
>> Oh dude, I don't have the new version of
of fuff cuz I'm pressing A and it's not
doing it.
>> Oh, it's like it's like a year old. You
haven't installed a long time.
>> No, it's it's like at least it's at
least a year old. Yeah,
>> you just press A.
>> Yeah.
>> Do I have to like add some sort of
interactive flag on it?
>> No, you hit enter deposit. Sorry.
>> Oh,
>> you don't hit A to deposit. You enter
deposit. Yeah. Now you just hit AFS to
add filter size.
>> If you do if if you do FS it will just
do like um filter size. But because
>> and then enter to resume.
>> Yeah. It just resumes it.
[laughter]
>> How did I not know about this?
>> Well, so this is why we're doing this
episode, right? Even like like you're
obviously a top hacker. You've used FFUF
a million times. You have a million
hacker friends, but like these little
tips can be like super beneficial.
>> Yeah, dude. Damn. Okay, that's sick.
Thanks for that. And you know what's
crazy, dude, is I'm looking at this.
Yeah. I mean, it definitely says h Man,
I I should have seen that. I should have
seen that. That's amazing. I've wasted
so much time with that, [laughter]
though.
>> Yeah, cuz you're like you're probably
like hitting control C and then like
tacking it on at the end or something,
aren't you? I am. Oh, no. It's so much
better. It's so much better. I just do
I'll do them um an autoc calibrate, but
then, you know, some will get through or
something. I'll hit enter and then just
do AFS because it'll it'll add it to the
filter. So, anyways.
>> Yeah. But and dude, sometimes like my
SSH session buffers if it's like, you
know, 403 bajillion 403s and I'm like,
"Okay, press C, control C, control C,
control C, control C." And it's like,
>> well, and then sometimes you run out of
the of the term history and you can't
actually go back and see that one cool
green hit you saw. You know what I'm
talking about? You get like a green hit,
then you get 403s, you control C it real
fast, and you can't get up to it. Yeah.
>> Wait, what do you mean green hit? Hold
up, hold up, hold up. Are you using like
coloring, too? Am I Am I like living?
>> You never use color in FFUF?
Oh my gosh, dude. You're joking.
rep color.
>> No, it's just dash c. Just dash c.
>> I can't. You use dude, do you visually
parse for the for the character 200
without just seeing green?
>> Yeah, I mean I do I do like I parse for
bracket like you know I I I tee it and
then I or like I pipe it to an output
file and then I No.
>> No way, dude. [laughter] Dude,
>> apparently I'm not a power user. No, I
mean literally like five years ago when
I started Bug Bounty and I was using
like freshlymade FFUF to fuzz um like
Verizon Media stuff just like waiting
just watching for the little green hits.
It's like tick tick tick whenever it
gets hits is like such a doping rush
from me. [laughter]
>> Yeah, it's I'm so shocked you haven't
like uh had that experience.
>> Wow, dude. All right. Well, I've got I'm
going to go read the uh the man page for
Fuff after this because apparently I
need to up my FUF game. To be to be fair
though, I actually don't use fuff very
often. Like I mostly I'll use automate
for targeted fuzzing inside of Kaido and
then you know when I'm brute forcing
which is very rare. Uh you know maybe
once or twice a week then I you know
then I'll use fuff. But um yeah
>> still man once or twice a week I should
I should I should know how to use fuff.
Damn it.
>> All [clears throat] right fine. All
right. Well hold on. Let me let me um
let me give a good one then since um
>> do it.
>> Yeah, dude. I I have to give a give a
shout out to uh JX Scout. I mean, we've
mentioned it a couple times on the pod,
but I've started using it recently,
especially in conjunction with Cursor.
And uh it's pretty freaking great to
have like
>> Yeah. So, tell me about it. I don't know
much about it at all.
>> Yeah. So, essentially what it does is it
>> is it a Chrome extension? Is it an app?
>> It's a It's a um plugin in Kaido. And
the Kaido plugin kind of sucks. It's
just like a hook for the command line
utility. Um, definitely some
improvements that could happen there,
but it uh hooks into Kaido, watches your
request history, looks at your scope,
and downloads all of the JS files,
beautifies them, puts them in a folder,
uh, and then we'll try to like enhance a
little bit too, you know, like,
[clears throat] uh, with uh, source maps
and, uh, you know, trying to find other
files to download and stuff like that.
Um,
>> so you just have VS Code pulled up with
that in it?
>> Yeah, I do. Yeah. And I I know that
there are um there's other I know that
there's JS Weasel and I and I think
there's some newer versions of JX Scout
that I kind of need to up uh update to.
>> Um but over like to be honest, it's it's
so it's good enough for me to like just
use it as is and then just hook cursor
into it because all I really need is the
JavaScript files there beautified and
then ready for me to throw AI at it,
right? And so then I'll just query AI
and I'll be like, "Okay, you know,
identify the pads. I you know, pull this
stuff out, you know, like and it'll just
jump through and read everything and and
uh especially with the massive context
window AIS, it's it's very good." Um
>> that's awesome.
>> Yeah. And you you just you know, your JS
is there when you need it, right? You
don't have to go download it and
whatever it is, it's there, you know? So
I I think that's really nice. It does
eat up dispace though, just FYI. It'll
eat this space like
>> um what was I going to say? Yeah, I
think like um so what do you do if the
are they often too large? What's your
go-to if it's too large?
>> It's it's not I mean this I haven't run
into that before with with it being too
too large. Um
>> I'm talking about for using AI like like
let's say yeah always switch to Gemini
Flash.
>> Yeah, I'm I'm doing I'm doing targeted
stuff anyway. I mean, like sometimes
I'll I'll switch the model specifically
to Gemini or whatever, but um uh you
know, a lot of times I'm doing more
targeted stuff like, okay, you know,
look at this block or or just the other
day I was like, hey, uh there's like
this super weird um GTS. What is it? I
think it's glitter or something. What
What is the
uh
GTS file? No. No. It's like there's
there was some weird file uh that was in
embedded inside of these JavaScript
files where it was like you know calling
functions with like bracket 40, you
know, I'm like oh this is so yucky. So I
just handed it to AI and was like
reverse this and give me readable
templiz JS and it like plopped it out. I
was like oh god I love you so much.
>> Nice.
>> Um so yeah I use it for that sort of
thing. I'll use it to say like, hey, you
know, identify, you know, the local
storage places or but to be honest, man,
I often just use it for VS Code
functions where I'm like, go to the
function definition, please, you know,
>> that's true. Just navigating around the
file is huge.
>> Yeah. And then I in cursor I've got
bookmarks, you know, I I've got like a
bookmarks extension that I can use to
like bookmark certain parts of code and
stuff like that to quickly navigate back
and forth. So yeah, it's it's pretty
solid.
>> That's huge.
J JS Scout plus uh plus cursor plus the
bookmarks extension. Really good stuff.
>> Yeah, I'm definitely going to use it
now. Um I just assumed it was like JS
Weasel or whatever. Like it was like
something kind of complex or something
you had to pay for or whatever.
>> Yeah, I think I want to say that. Yeah,
there is. I think there's like a premium
version of JX Scout and um there's also
a VS code extension that you can use
that will like parse the A tree and like
um identify paths and like pull a bunch
of stuff out kind of like JS weasel
does. Um but to be honest, man, like
just having it downloaded and grabbing
the source maps and like you know doing
its thing I think is is pretty solid. So
there's like a command line component
that downloads everything. There's a
Kaido component for the plugin. Then
there's like a a VS Code extension if
you want to as well. So, there's lots of
components.
>> Sweet.
>> Yeah.
>> Um, one thing I was going to mention,
which is this is just super dumb, but I
I'm sure there are some people out there
who don't know about it. I um
uh often in the last couple live hacking
events or whatever have um seen or like
just had a really strong use for
actually I want to talk to you about it
afterwards for this like school app that
uh my kids use at their school. But
anyways, I've just used the Mac
systemwide proxy. Um so I was just going
to tell people how to use it real quick.
If you have a Mac, you can probably tell
them how to use it on Windows, but if
you just go to Wi-Fi settings, it's
actually kind of annoying to find
sometimes, but if you just like go to
Wi-Fi settings and then click details
next to the connected Wi-Fi, um you can
just set up like a systemwide proxy. And
[snorts] so I'll just throw it you have
to have installed, you know, the
Kaidoert into your um keychain, but you
can just proxy the entire system. And so
that's a lot of times that's useful if
you're testing like a desktop app or
just something that's more difficult to
proxy.
>> Yeah. Hopefully there's not pinning,
man. like like freaking
>> Have you had that? And like um
electronics?
>> I've had it. Yeah, it's super annoying,
you know, like like desktop apps and
yeah, it's bad. But yeah, system level
proxies definitely helpful for hitting
those those uh desktop apps and and it
can be easy wins too. Everybody thinks,
you know, hacking these desktop apps are
really hard. If you can just proxy it
and then get to the APIs, then you're
just web hacking again, you know.
>> Yep. Exactly.
>> So
>> yeah, the thing actually I'll go ahead
and mention on the pod because I'm sure
some people might be able to give us
good advice for it. The thing that I was
going to ask you, the app that I want to
test, um, because it allows you to like
see what your kids are browsing from
their school, which is just kind of
crazy, is is like a HTTP2 gRPC.
>> And dude, it's nasty. It's really nasty.
It's like cuz one, Kaido doesn't support
HB2. So, I'm using like burp free
edition, but then uh the copy to curl
from Kaido
>> uh doesn't seem to work um whenever I
then try to pipe it into burp. Um and
then in burp, you can't even really edit
it very well because you know how like
when you're trying to actually edit like
the bites,
>> it's a pain. Yeah.
>> For um anyways, it's just a really weird
protocol. Uh, but I almost could
guarantee it's going to be vulnerable
and I, you know, I feel like impact on
seeing what kids are browsing to on
their computers, like being able to see
what all the students are browsing to is
such high impact. And I just care about
I care about securing it for my kids.
So,
>> Exactly. Yeah. totally, man. I I think
HTTP2, you know, right now, did you try
a downgrade? Like, does it does it
support HTTP1 if you downgrade it or
>> It doesn't. Yeah, it doesn't.
>> Yeah. I mean, then you're stuck using
Burp there. Uh but yeah, I I think that
one of the things that I have had
success with though is is getting a like
if you if you can get AI to um poke at
you to like get the request.
>> That's true. I should I should have had
AI use Python to do it. It would
probably be a lot cleaner like hey
here's my token. You poke at this. Yeah.
>> Exactly. Yeah. Yeah. Um so might go
after that. Okay. Um, we've only got a
couple more minutes, but uh, I was gonna
mention, dude, I know Matan pointed this
out in his episode that we did, and so a
lot of the like diehard listeners have
heard it, but I'm going to repeat it
again for everybody. Conditional
breakpoints in DevTools are massive.
Like one, you don't need to be pressing,
you know, next next every single time
you're trying to set like a breakpoint
and load into something. Um, and you can
use conditional breakpoints not only for
their actual purpose, which is, you
know, conditionally triggering a
breakpoint, but you can use conditional
breakpoint to run arbitrary JS code at a
specific spot in the execution script
without having to use match and replace
and dealing with like, you know,
>> I know a guy that's been using that for
testing feature flags.
>> Yeah, it's Oh, it's Yeah. Well, who's
that guy? You know,
>> I don't know [laughter]
>> who that guy who could that guy possibly
be. Um, but I use it all the time for
testing feature flag. [laughter]
Um, and it's just very helpful, right?
Because feature flag stuff, there's
always a function that's parsing the
feature flags and being like, should I
turn this on, should I not? And you just
say like yes for everything.
>> Um, so the way that I do it is typically
like, you know, use um parenthesis or
whatever and then put whatever you want
to do, comma, false. So it just returns
false uh always which is which will not
trigger the conditional breakpoint but
it does run the JS code. Um and I just
you know it's hacky it's it's messy but
that's the kind of [__] we like you know
like and it and it gets the job done
really quick when you need to run some
JS code at a specific point. Um
>> yeah how do I I I still find DevTools um
breakpoint system to be like confusing
and annoying. Like sometimes they all
disappear, sometimes they don't get
triggered. It's like
>> Yeah. Yeah. No, it's a pain. And then
sometimes you you use the little like
disable all breakpoints button and then
it still does it like it still breaks on
them. I'm like frick stop, you know, and
then I got to go in there and like
>> uh you know delete all of or uncheck all
the break points with the like uncheck
all button and then I disabled the one
that I wanted and it's like that
interface could really really use a
facelift in my opinion.
>> Yeah. Cool. Would you want to rapid fire
these last few?
>> Yeah. Okay. So rapid fire. Um all right,
you next. Go. I just
>> All right, cool. I I'll rapid fire both
of mine and then you can clear out your
list.
>> I for this event um did something pretty
cool. ChatgPT Atlas is like good enough
where it's like actually usable and I've
heard perplexity comment is actually
like more than usable like pretty fast
at like basically doing things in the
browser. And so like for hacking it's
kind of useful kind of not. But what I
found it to be really useful for and I
think other hackers will too is
basically setting up things. So, like
let's say you're try you're trying to
like set up a new um I'm trying to think
of like an example of stuff I haven't
hacked uh or like things. Anyways,
you're trying to set up a new SAS or
like let's say okay, actually here's a
great example. You're inside of GCP,
right? And you're trying to set up some
new service and you're like confused and
you're annoyed, you don't really care
and you know whatever. You like open up
Chat GP Atlas and say, "Hey, here you're
inside my GCP account. Don't do anything
that's going to cost me a bunch of
money, but go spin up a VM or whatever
or go enable this service, right?" And
it's like it'll it'll do its own
research. It'll browse around. It can
click around. It can kind of figure it
out for you, which is really cool and
really useful. There probably are some
implications for like crawling a site
more intelligently than just like using
Katana that you could also use this for
if you were proxying. But
>> anyways, I thought that was I thought
that was really cool. Second thing is um
a completely different tip which is
terminal notifier. There's probably an
equivalent on Windows, but there's this
Mac thing called terminal notifier and
it gives you like a notification. I um
in my system prompt for um codeex and
claude code have it use a terminal
notifier whenever it's done. So it like
can ping me and let me know that it's
done working because I find myself
getting distracted and like an hour
later I'm like oh crap I had this thing
writing code for me in the background
and it now has asked me a question and I
want to know about that question. Um I
think there's also like basically a way
to like they're called hooks where you
can hook in where it doesn't even have
to choose to notify you. just like
always run some snippet of code when
it's at like a stopping point. I'm
pretty sure they're called hooks if
anybody wants to look into that. But
anyways, those are two tips I wanted to
bring up.
>> Yeah. Are you talking about when the
command is done running or are you
talking about when it hits like a pause
point?
>> Um both, but specifically a pause point.
>> Oh, really? Yeah, the pause point is
interesting. I I uh I haven't found
anything that does that. Uh, I have used
like something like notify sh or project
discoveries notify to like get like a,
you know, discord ping or whatever when
my done or I actually had an alias on
one of my laptops. I don't think I
transferred it over but it would go
beep. You know, I could just say like
pipe it into beep or like and and beep
and whenever it was done it would go
beep, you know.
>> Daniel Masler has one that uh pipes it
into another AI which summarized what it
did and it immediately talks to him out
loud at his desk. So, it'll just like
it'll be like I just completed the task
that you gave me. [laughter]
>> It appears as if this task has been
completed. Here is the summary. So,
>> exactly. Exactly.
>> Yeah. All right. Thanks, Jarvis. Um,
yeah, Dan would have Jarvis. Um, all
right. Do you have a hard stop right now
or can I rapid fire these?
>> You can rapid fire yours.
>> Okay, I'm gonna rapid fire these. Um, I
talk about Kaido a lot. So, this is
mostly for the people in the Kaido
ecosystem because I am in the Kaido
ecosystem and that's what I hack with.
So, that's what you're going to get. But
you can also think about how to do these
things in burp if you are not using
Kaido. Also, JX app that I mentioned
earlier does have a Burp extension as
well. Um, okay. So, top level navigation
highlighter. I cannot like say this
enough. I know I've said it time and
time again. You guys are probably sick
of hearing me say it. If you are not
using this, you are in the stone age.
Like, it is
>> it's on by default. I think I
>> I don't know that they turned it on by
default because people were like, you
know,
>> I think they turned it off. It was
definitely on by default for a while. I
used it.
>> Oh, was it? Okay. Yeah, you got to be
using color navigations in Kaido as a
passive workflow. That is just
non-negotiable at this point. Like it is
just so much better. Okay. So, you will
be able to navigate so much quickly. So
much more quickly.
>> At the very at the very least, it is
installed into Kaido. It might not be
enabled, but you just go to pass
workflows and you enable it. And then
anytime there's a top level nav in your
browser, it'll get highlighted a
specific color. And it's it helps just
like bookmark what you're doing to even
if you're just scrolling really fast
through history and you're like, "What
was I doing?" your eyes will jump to
those colors and you'll be able to find
requests so much faster.
>> Yeah, that was ah that was five top
level navigations ago, you know, like
okay I it just gives you much more you
understand where things are in HP
history much better.
>> Um
next is shift which we've talked about
before but I went through my shift
queries and I identified what I most use
them for and here they are.
>> Um adding quick and dirty match and
replace rules is number one. I do that
all the time with shift. I never use the
match and replace interface anymore. I
just tell shift to do it. Uh, generating
quick word lists with specific things
that I want in them. So, you know, you
know, one to 100 line word lists. Um,
>> when Justin was typing that out, he
actually said quick workouts. So,
apparently [laughter] he uses shift to
generate his workouts as well.
>> Dude, why are you watching me type in
the doc, man? I'm like, [snorts]
give me like
>> give me like taba, you know, give me
like a taba thing to to do. Oh my gosh,
dude. I sound like in I just said tabata
in English and that sounded horrible.
>> Oh gosh,
>> I don't even know what that is.
>> Anyway, uh it's it's one of those like
hit workouts, right? So, you know, you
can do like, you know, burpees,
>> lunge jacks, you know, right?
>> Yeah. Tabata. Yeah.
>> Oh, is that how you say it in English?
>> I think that's how you say it in
English. I've never heard it in any
other language.
>> Yeah.
>> Well, sure. Anyways, that makes sense.
More shift tips.
>> Okay. Um I use it to mass modify JSON.
So, hey, you know, add some tags here,
you know, modify the casing here, you
know, do that. Um, I use it to generate
uh HTTPQL queries and I use it to update
filters. So, those are the those main um
uses that I use ship for.
>> Um, drop is super helpful and expedites
the workflow a ton if you are
collaborating with people. Super easy to
set up, super clean.
>> Um, definitely use it. Uh, and then the
last one that I'm going to do is
>> because everyone for literally
everyone's still in the stone age.
They're literally copying and pasting
raw HTTP into Discord. Then the person
has to copy it. Then they have to send a
natural request because otherwise, you
know, in Burp and Kaido both whenever
you paste it in, you have to set the
host header. And so it's like um
normally what I always do, and I'm sure
you do this too, you go find a similar
request
>> that you know is to the same host, which
is sometimes annoying and also costing
you time to send the replay so that when
you paste it in, you don't have to edit
the host editor. Right.
>> Exactly. And so now you can just right
click, drop it to Justin. So much
easier.
>> So much freaking easier, dude. Drop is
beautiful. Drop is really beautiful. Um,
and then last but not least, there's
DevTools. So for any uh in in Kaido,
okay, so this is not the dev panel uh
you know that you see in the browser.
This is a hot reload script in Kaido
that reinstalls your plugin every time
you push code changes. If you're not
using this when you're doing Kaido dev,
I don't know how you're doing it because
it's a pain to manually reinstall and
uninstall the plugin every time. So, um,
those are our hacking workflow tips for
you guys. Hope you enjoyed that. I know
it was a, uh, little bit of a rapid fire
episode with a little bit here, a little
bit there, but um, yeah. And I, I guess
these things have really made a
difference in my hacking workflow and I
learned a ton as well from you, Reszo,
today. I'm so excited for that for that
pup stuff.
>> Yeah. Yeah, dude. Yeah. I'll have to
show you later.
>> All right, sounds good. Ready? Ready to
bounce. All right. Peace.
>> Peace, guys. That's fun.
And that's a wrap on this episode of
Critical Thinking. Thanks so much for
watching to the end, y'all. If you want
more critical thinking content, uh,
[music] or if you want to support the
show, head over to ctbb.show/isord.
You can hop in the community. There's
lots of great highlevel hacking
discussion happening there on top of
master classes, [music] hackalongs,
exclusive content, and a full-time
hunters guild. If you're a full-time
hunter, [music] it's a great time. Trust
me. All right, I'll see you there.